[
  {
    "season": 1,
    "episode": 1,
    "airDate": "2025-07-07",
    "name": "America, Animals, Famous People, Fruits, Disney",
    "title": "ü¶Ö America, üê® Animals, üë©‚ÄçüöÄ Famous People, üçç Fruits, üê≠ Disney",
    "youTubeUrl": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VsV-6ejJ-OY",
    "spotifyUrl": "https://open.spotify.com/episode/1vrxg4KrtqcI8OYw9J2rbY?si=_gf5bQZxRJazuaYB0TyacQ",
    "applePodcastsUrl": "https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/ep-1-america-animals-famous-people-fruits-disney/id1834272891?i=1000722717873",
    "categories":
    [
      {
        "name": "America",
        "emojis": "ü¶Ö",
        "questions":
        [
          {
            "question": "In what state will you find the Statue of Liberty?",
            "answer": "New York"
          },
          {
            "question": "In what famous Arizona canyon can you find Pink Rattlesnakes?",
            "answer": "The Grand Canyon"
          },
          {
            "question": "What city is known most as the gambling capital of the US?",
            "answer": "Las Vegas"
          },
          {
            "question": "In what two states will you find Disneyland and Disney World?",
            "answer": "California and Florida"
          },
          {
            "question": "The Wright Brothers first flew a plane in what state?",
            "answer": "(Kitty Hawk) North Carolina"
          },
          {
            "question": "What windy US city is known for its Deep Dish Pizzas?",
            "answer": "Chicago"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "name": "Animals",
        "emojis": "üê®",
        "questions":
        [
          {
            "question": "What is the world's largest animal?",
            "answer": "The Blue Whale"
          },
          {
            "question": "What dog breed is Snoopy?",
            "answer": "A Beagle"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the state animal of Oregon?",
            "answer": "The Beaver"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the horned whale, also known as the 'Unicorn of the Sea'?",
            "answer": "The Narwhal"
          },
          {
            "question": "The Humuhumunukunukuapua'a is the state fish for what state?",
            "answer": "Hawaii"
          },
          {
            "question": "The mascot for the University of Michigan is also the name of what long-clawed X-Man superhero?",
            "answer": "Wolverine"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "name": "Famous People",
        "emojis": "üë©‚ÄçüöÄ",
        "questions":
        [
          {
            "question": "Who was the first US President?",
            "answer": "George Washington"
          },
          {
            "question": "What holiday do most states celebrate on the second Monday of January?",
            "answer": "Martin Luther King Jr. Day"
          },
          {
            "question": "Who is the famous Dutch painter who cut off his own ear?",
            "answer": "Vincent Van Gogh"
          },
          {
            "question": "What Japanese born baseball player signed the biggest baseball contract ever in 2023?",
            "answer": "Shohei Ohtani"
          },
          {
            "question": "What basketball players starred in Space Jam?",
            "answer": "Michael Jordan and Lebron James"
          },
          {
            "question": "What famous author, activist, and lecturer was blind and deaf when she was a 19 month old child?",
            "answer": "Helen Keller"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "name": "Fruits",
        "emojis": "üçç",
        "questions":
        [
          {
            "question": "What fruit known for being grown in Georgia is famous for having 'fuzz'?",
            "answer": "The Peach"
          },
          {
            "question": "What fruit shares its name with a mythical creature from Shrek?",
            "answer": "Dragonfruit"
          },
          {
            "question": "What stinky fruit from Asia has a spikey outer covering?",
            "answer": "The Durian"
          },
          {
            "question": "What kind of fruit is named after your belly button?",
            "answer": "The Navel Orange"
          },
          {
            "question": "What fruity ice cream flavor is kinda named after the lead singer from The Grateful Dead?",
            "answer": "Cherry (Jerry) Garcia"
          },
          {
            "question": "The prune is the dried up version of what fruit?",
            "answer": "The Plum"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "name": "Disney",
        "emojis": "üê≠",
        "questions":
        [
          {
            "question": "What is the name of Jasmine's tiger in Aladdin?",
            "answer": "Rajah"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the biggest movie of all time in ticket sales?",
            "answer": "Inside Out 2"
          },
          {
            "question": "Dwayne Johnson voiced what shape-changing Disney character?",
            "answer": "Maui"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the boy who owns Woody in Toy Story (I)?",
            "answer": "Andy"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of Mr. Incredible's ice-cold friend?",
            "answer": "Frozone"
          }
        ]
      }
    ],
    "notes": ""
  },
  {
    "season": 1,
    "episode": 2,
    "airDate": "2025-07-14",
    "name": "Musical Films, Europe, Technology, Insects, Dog Man",
    "title": "üé∂üé• Musical Films, üá™üá∫ Europe, üíª Technology, üêù Insects, üê∂üï∫ Dog Man",
    "youTubeUrl": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AkdAIwcJeVU",
    "spotifyUrl": "https://open.spotify.com/episode/40kSxrSrtpL67GXPzhJhNj?si=vNP-qUmYRYCsdJWNjb7cUQ",
    "applePodcastsUrl": "https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/ep-2-musical-films-europe-technology-insects-dog-man/id1834272891?i=1000722718038",
    "categories":
    [
      {
        "name": "Musical Films",
        "emojis": "üé∂üé•",
        "questions":
        [
          {
            "question": "What 1964 musical starring Julie Andrews is about a magical flying nanny?",
            "answer": "Mary Poppins"
          },
          {
            "question": "What 2022 musical about a schoolgirl with magical powers stars a cast of Revolting Children?",
            "answer": "Matilda: The Musical"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the school that Elphaba and Glinda attend in Wicked?",
            "answer": "Shiz"
          },
          {
            "question": "In the 1971 film Willie Wonka and the Chocolate Factory, what is the full name of the kid that takes over the factory?",
            "answer": "Charlie Bucket"
          },
          {
            "question": "What sport did Troy playin the 2006 film High School Musical?",
            "answer": "Basketball"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "name": "Europe",
        "emojis": "üá™üá∫",
        "questions":
        [
          {
            "question": "What boot shaped European country is known for its delicious pasta dishes?",
            "answer": "Italy"
          },
          {
            "question": "What European nation has the smallest population with fewer than 1000 people?",
            "answer": "Vatican City"
          },
          {
            "question": "The character Dracula comes from what European country?",
            "answer": "Romania"
          },
          {
            "question": "What European country and home to Socrates, Plato, and Aristotle is known as the birthplace of Western Philosophy?",
            "answer": "Greece"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the primary currency used in the United Kingdom?",
            "answer": "The Pound (¬£)"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "name": "Technology",
        "emojis": "üíª",
        "questions":
        [
          {
            "question": "What Korean technology company is the world's biggest producer of Android phones?",
            "answer": "Samsung"
          },
          {
            "question": "What does \"GPS\" stand for regarding navigation technology?",
            "answer": "Global Positioning System"
          },
          {
            "question": "What short range wireless technology was named for a Scandinavian warrior king?",
            "answer": "Bluetooth"
          },
          {
            "question": "The use of what technology really took off during COVID when people had to look at restaurant menus on their phones?",
            "answer": "QR Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "Large Language Models (LLMs) such as Gemini, DeepSeek, and ChatGPT are platforms for what two-word technology?",
            "answer": "Artificial Intelligence (AI)"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "name": "Insects",
        "emojis": "üêù",
        "questions":
        [
          {
            "question": "What tiny Marvel superhero played by Paul Rudd is named after an insect?",
            "answer": "Ant-Man"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the hexagonal structure that bees create in their beehives?",
            "answer": "Honeycombs"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the most famous Mexican song about a Cockroach?",
            "answer": "La Cucaracha"
          },
          {
            "question": "What chirping insect is known for rubbing its wings together to make music on warm Summer nights?",
            "answer": "The Cricket"
          },
          {
            "question": "What type of insect is known for destroying wood?",
            "answer": "The Termite"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "name": "Dog Man",
        "emojis": "üê∂üï∫",
        "questions":
        [
          {
            "question": "What is Dog Man's job?",
            "answer": "Police Officer"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the human part of Dog Man?",
            "answer": "Officer Knight"
          },
          {
            "question": "Who wrote the Dog Man books?",
            "answer": "Dav Pilkey"
          },
          {
            "question": "The author of Dog Man also wrote what series of books about a principal in his tighty whiteys?",
            "answer": "The Adventures of Captain Underpants"
          },
          {
            "question": "The tagline for the 2025 movie Dog Man is 'Part dog...part man...all...' what??",
            "answer": "All Hero"
          }
        ]
      }
    ],
    "notes": ""
  },
  {
    "season": 1,
    "episode": 3,
    "airDate": "2025-07-21",
    "name": "Kid Songs, Ice Cream, Video Games, The Body, Bluey",
    "title": "üëßüèªüé∂ Kid Songs, üç¶ Ice Cream, üëæ Video Games, üí™ The Body, üíôüê∂ Bluey",
    "youTubeUrl": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DnVFDo-7kgM",
    "spotifyUrl": "https://open.spotify.com/episode/2g0MiOMc3eooJ6b1kI8whS?si=4nmT1yb2RzmogI3VJ_Rprw",
    "applePodcastsUrl": "https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/ep-3-kid-songs-ice-cream-video-games-the-body-bluey/id1834272891?i=1000722717907",
    "categories":
    [
      {
        "name": "Kid Songs",
        "emojis": "üé∂üé•",
        "questions":
        [
          {
            "question": "In the song Hickory Dickory Dock, what animal ran up and down the clock?",
            "answer": "The Mouse"
          },
          {
            "question": "The American Alphabet Song is sung to the tune of what song about something shiny in the night sky?",
            "answer": "Twinkle Twinkle Little Star"
          },
          {
            "question": "In the song Baby Shark, how many \"doo's\" to they sing after every type of shark?",
            "answer": "Six"
          },
          {
            "question": "In the song On Top of Spaghetti, the meatball fell off the table when somebody did...what?",
            "answer": "When somebody sneezed"
          },
          {
            "question": "What did the doctor tell Mama Monkey when all her babies kept getting hurt falling off the bed?",
            "answer": "\"No more monkeys jumping on the bed!\""
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "name": "Ice Cream",
        "emojis": "üç¶",
        "questions":
        [
          {
            "question": "What ice cream store founded in Glendale, CA, in 1945 is famous for always having at least 31 flavors?",
            "answer": "Baskin-Robbins"
          },
          {
            "question": "What green colored ice cream is popular at Japanese restaurants?",
            "answer": "Green Tea (Matcha) Ice Cream"
          },
          {
            "question": "What type of ice cream is popular at Mexican Restaurants and has a warm and crunchy outer layer?",
            "answer": "Deep Fried Ice Cream"
          },
          {
            "question": "What cold Italian treat is made with more milk and less cream than regular ice cream?",
            "answer": "Gelato"
          },
          {
            "question": "What bumpy ice cream flavor is Sloth's favorite from the 1985 film The Goonies?",
            "answer": "Rocky Road"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "name": "Video Games",
        "emojis": "üëæ",
        "questions":
        [
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the big boss in The Legend of Zelda series?",
            "answer": "Ganon (or Ganondorf)"
          },
          {
            "question": "In Minecraft, what are the green creatures that explode when they get close to you?",
            "answer": "Creepers"
          },
          {
            "question": "In Animal Crossing, what is the anme of the museum's owl curator?",
            "answer": "Blathers"
          },
          {
            "question": "Which company originally created Call of Duty?",
            "answer": "Blizzard | Activision"
          },
          {
            "question": "In the Angry Birds game, what color are the enemy Pigs?",
            "answer": "Green"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "name": "The Body",
        "emojis": "üí™",
        "questions":
        [
          {
            "question": "What organ is the pump that pushes blood through the circulatory system?",
            "answer": "The Heart"
          },
          {
            "question": "How many bones are in the adult human body?",
            "answer": "206"
          },
          {
            "question": "Which toe represents the Piggy that went \"Wee Wee Wee\" all the way home?",
            "answer": "The Pinky Toe"
          },
          {
            "question": "What body part helps you taste food?",
            "answer": "The Tongue"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of a small, hard, thickened area of the skin on the foot that sounds like it could be a big lump with knobs?",
            "answer": "A Corn"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "name": "Bluey",
        "emojis": "üíôüê∂",
        "questions":
        [
          {
            "question": "What is Bingo's favorite stuffed animal?",
            "answer": "Floppy"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of Bluey's grey colored cousin?",
            "answer": "Muffin"
          },
          {
            "question": "What color is Bluey's sister, Bingo?",
            "answer": "Orange"
          },
          {
            "question": "What city and country are home to Bluey's family?",
            "answer": "Brisbane, Australia"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of Bluey's mother?",
            "answer": "Chilli"
          }
        ]
      }
    ],
    "notes": ""
  },
  {
    "season": 1,
    "episode": 4,
    "airDate": "2025-08-15",
    "name": "Cars, Vegetables, The Color Blue, Math, and Star Wars",
    "title": "üöò Cars, ü•¶ Vegetables, üü¶ The Color Blue, üßÆ Math, and üí´ Star Wars",
    "youTubeUrl": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=f47AZ5oFaZc",
    "spotifyUrl": "https://open.spotify.com/episode/45EGJZKPB1ID2erY9llTDd?si=bvL9C2WdSeOl06uzassd5Q",
    "applePodcastsUrl": "https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/ep-4-cars-vegetables-the-color-blue-math-and-star-wars/id1834272891?i=1000722717906",
    "categories":
    [
      {
        "name": "Cars",
        "emojis": "üöò",
        "questions":
        [
          {
            "question": "What is the name for the type of car that is powered by BOTH gasoline and electricity?",
            "answer": "Hybrid"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name for the metal covering that you open to expose the ENGINE in a car?",
            "answer": "The Hood"
          },
          {
            "question": "What do people often wrap around their tires when driving through snow?",
            "answer": "Tire Chains (Snow Chains)"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is another name for a car's front passenger seat that got it's name back in the stagecoach days?",
            "answer": "The Shotgun seat"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the floor pedal used to stop the car?",
            "answer": "The brake"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "name": "Vegetables",
        "emojis": "ü•¶",
        "questions":
        [
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the Vegetable drink that uses 8 different types of Vegetables?",
            "answer": "V8"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the small round leafy vegetable that sounds like they're from BELGIUM?",
            "answer": "Brussels Sprouts"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the brown tuber vegetable used to make French fries?",
            "answer": "Potatoes"
          },
          {
            "question": "What layered vegetable often makes people CRY when they cut it?",
            "answer": "The Onion"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the name of the green pod vegetable served in Japanese Restaurants under the name edamame?",
            "answer": "Soy Beans"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "name": "The Color Blue",
        "emojis": "üü¶",
        "questions":
        [
          {
            "question": "What popular salad dressing is often used with hot wings?",
            "answer": "Bleu Cheese"
          },
          {
            "question": "What professional Major League baseball team is named after a blue bird and is based in Toronto?",
            "answer": "The Blue Jays"
          },
          {
            "question": "What computer company was also known as BIG BLUE?",
            "answer": "IBM"
          },
          {
            "question": "This prize is often awarded at state fairs for the best animal or farm grown food item.",
            "answer": "The Blue Ribbon"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the LARGEST animal on Earth?",
            "answer": "The Blue Whale"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "name": "Math",
        "emojis": "üßÆ",
        "questions":
        [
          {
            "question": "How many different outcomes can you have if you flip a penny two times?",
            "answer": "Four"
          },
          {
            "question": "How many sides are there on an Octagon?",
            "answer": "Eight"
          },
          {
            "question": "What can you multiply any number with to get the same number as the result?",
            "answer": "One"
          },
          {
            "question": "In the US, March 14th is a day that celebrates what special number?",
            "answer": "Pi (3.14)"
          },
          {
            "question": "If you drive 30 miles an hour for two hours, how far have you traveled?",
            "answer": "60 Miles"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "name": "Star Wars",
        "emojis": "üí´",
        "questions":
        [
          {
            "question": "Approximately how old is Baby Yoda?",
            "answer": "50 years old"
          },
          {
            "question": "What cute furry creatures live on the moon Endor?",
            "answer": "Ewoks"
          },
          {
            "question": "Frank Oz, the puppeteer who voiced Yoda, also voiced what blue Sesame Street character with nearly the same voice?",
            "answer": "Grover"
          },
          {
            "question": "What color is Yoda's light saber?",
            "answer": "Green"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is Princess Leia's home planet?",
            "answer": "Alderaan"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
]